ZiMuZu
倾情奉献
翻译
草草
磁芯章鱼X
翻译
木浅薰
小酸奶!
翻译
吃冰棒
电脑团
翻译
TL
时间轴
大葱ALX  念念  今
电脑狂人
第四季
第二集
校对&总监
草草
后期
饿得慌
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
风投
怎么回事
What happened?
他...
He...
认识了别人
met someone else.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
你...
Are -- are you...
离婚了吗
Divorced?
我是想问没事吧  但是...
I was gonna say "Okay," But...
没事
Yes.
应该没事
Yeah, I-I guess I am.
那  你离婚了吗
So, are you divorced?
快了
Almost.
在日本处理这些事真的很麻烦
You know, it's a pain in the ass doing it from Japan.
得填各种表格  去好几趟邮局
So there's all these forms and trips to the post office
往德州寄材料
and sending stuff to Texas.
感觉一切都像一个奇怪的梦
And it all feels like this weird dream...
结婚  去东京...
...being married and Tokyo...
对不起
I'm sorry.
你想听我说吗
Do you want to hear this?
你说什么我都愿意听
I want to hear whatever you want to tell me.
我感觉自己像个傻子
I feel like an idiot.
你不是傻子
You're not an idiot.
也许有些冲动
Impulsive, maybe.
好吧  乔
Okay, Joe.
我也很冲动  所以...
I'm impulsive, too, so...
你...准备留在加州吗
Are you, uh -- are you gonna stay in California?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是我该离开这个宾馆
I should get out of this hotel, though.
这里的淋浴太差了  我想好好泡个澡
The shower sucks, and I really want a bath.
我在日本经常泡澡
I took a lot of baths in Japan.
我喜欢泡澡
I love a good bath.
是啊
Yeah.
不给点游戏的提示吗
So, no hints about this game, huh?
不给  你得自己想明白
No. You got to figure it out yourself.
但是太难了
But it's so hard.
等你想出来
It is until you figure it out.
就不难了
And then it isn't.
是谁
Who was it?
什么是谁
Who was what?
跟汤姆...的那女人
The woman that Tom...
这个...
That's, uh...
这是最有趣的部分  我都没问
That's the best part. I never even asked.
跟我说话  跟我说点什么
Talk to me. Tell me something.
跟你说什么
Tell you what?
就...我不知道  随便  人间生活
Just -- I don't know -- anything, life on Earth.
我都错过了什么
What'd I miss?
你想听什么
Well, what do you want to hear?
-乔  跟我说说话  -好吧
- Joe, just talk to me. - Okay.
你知道比尔·克林顿是现在的总统吗
Did you know that Bill Clinton is the president?
知道  日本人很喜欢他
Yeah. They love him in Japan.
那些芝士汉堡
All those cheeseburgers.
还有什么
So, what else?
牛仔队赢了超级碗杯
The Cowboys won the Super Bowl.
奥黛丽·赫本死了  瑞弗·菲尼克斯也死了
Audrey Hepburn died. And so did River Phoenix.
有几个疯子想炸掉世贸中心  还有...
some crazies tried to blow up the World Trade Center, and,
你可以在军队里做同性恋
you can be gay in the military,
但是别人不能问你
but nobody can ask you about it,
你也不能告诉别人
and you can't tell anybody.
你知道IBM损失了50亿吗
Did you know IBM lost $5 billion?
他们查过沙发垫下面吗
They check the couch cushions?
戈登经历了一个养生阶段
You know, Gordon went through this whole health phase.
他家里有个房间全是健身器材
He's got a room in his house full of gym stuff.
他买了一个诺迪克跑步机
Like, he's got this NordicTrack
还有什么屁股塑形大师
and something called a ButtMaster, so...
然后  我也遇到了一件事
And, um, this thing happened to me.
我去西夫韦超市时  下车后
I was getting out of my car at a Safeway,
看到一个女人在挥舞着手臂
and I saw this woman flailing her arms, just --
一群蜜蜂在袭击她
A swarm of bees was attacking her,
不停地叮她
just stinging her again and again, you know?
她摔倒在地
And she fell to the ground.
然后一辆冰激凌车
And out of nowhere,
不知道从哪里钻出来冲过停车场
this ice-cream truck comes screaming through the parking lot,
还放着《骗中骗》[叮咬]的音乐
and it's playing that music from The Sting.
那个人从车上跑下来
And the guy gets out of the -- the truck,
开始对她做心肺复苏什么的
and he's doing CPR and everything.
那辆车还在放叮叮咚咚的钢琴曲
And the truck is still playing that tinkling piano music,
救护车到了后  还在继续放
and it keeps playing it even after the ambulance arrives.
我那几天满脑子都是那件事
And it's all I could think about for days,
那些医护人员
these paramedics
就着这背景音乐  疯狂地抢救她
just working on her like crazy while this music played
那可能是她最后听到的东西
and how that might be the last thing she ever hears.
卡梅伦
Cameron?
卡梅
Cam?
我就继续说吧
I'll just keep talking
因为我觉得
'cause I think you're --
我觉得你还在听
I think you're still there.
你在听吗
Are you there?
我在呢
I'm here.
喂
Hello?
我刚刚在泡茶
I was just making some tea.
你想知道你的名字在夏威夷叫什么吗
Do you want to know what your Hawaiian name is?
说说
Okay.
是卡梅拉诺
It's Kamelonu.
有一个网站可以...
See, there's this whole website where you --
你一直没挂吗
You didn't hang up?
是啊  我得告诉你我的名字在夏威夷叫什么
Well, yeah, I had to tell you my Hawaiian name.
是什么
What is it?
就是乔  只不过第一个字母是I
It's just Joe, but with an I instead of a J.
"姚"吗
Eye-oh-ee?
其实我觉得应该读"哟"
I actually think that's it's "Yo."
对吧
Right?
好吧  我不会叫你哟的
Right. I'm not calling you "Yo."
这真像是卡梅拉诺会说的话
That is such a Kamelonu thing to say.
圣何塞真奇怪
San Jose is so weird.
你知道那里其实比旧金山要大吗
You know it's actually bigger than San Francisco?
我知道  但是看上去小多了  对吧
I know, but it seems so much smaller, doesn't it?
我觉得我看到了一个水上公园
I think I see a water park.
我12岁后就再没玩过水滑梯
I haven't ridden a water slide since I was twelve.
那是不是很奇怪
Isn't that weird?
你可能已经玩了你人生中最后一次水滑梯
You might have already been on your last water slide.
不可能  我一直想买下一个水上公园
No way. I always planned on buying up a water park,
一个人住在那里  到晚上就去滑水道
living there alone, riding the flumes by night.
是吗
Yeah?
这就是你长大后想做的事吗
That's what you wanted to do when you grew up?
老实说  我觉得我一直是个大人
Honestly, I feel like I've always been a grown up.
我猜你是唯一一个下巴棱角分明的
Well, I bet you were one of the only babies
小婴儿
with a chiseled jawline.
不  其实还有一个
No, there was one other kid,
但是我们打了个你死我活
but we fought to the death.
你对流浪者怎么看
What do you think about Rover?
流浪者
Rover?
他们很聪明
They're...smart,
要价低
pivot on a dime,
团队协作很好
good team dynamics.
是啊  但你不觉得艾略特和维拉
Yeah, but doesn't it seem like Elliot and Vera
有时候想杀了对方吗
just want to kill each other sometimes?
那是因为他们是夫妻
That's because they're married.
那怪不得了
Yeah, that makes sense.
你该知道
You should just know that
他们每晚开车回家的时候
they're gonna talk major shit about you
都会说你不少坏话了
on the drive home every night.
我
About me?
我准备让你来负责流浪者
I'm making you lead on Rover.
是你把他们捡了出来
You pulled them off the slush pile.
你几个月来一直做着投资经理的工作
You've been doing the work of an associate for months now.
你准备好了
You're ready.
今天带他们去孵化器安顿下来
Get them set up in the Incubator today,
并开始给我找个新助理
and start looking for my new assistant.
找到之前  你暂时要身兼二职
Until we find one, you'll be pulling double duty.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
现在一般是人类
This is typically where members of the human race
表达狂喜或...
express some enthusiasm or...
谢谢你
Thank you.
今天谁赢了
Who's winning today?
海莉·克拉克
Haley Clark.
小姑娘  给我一个充分的理由
Young lady, tell me there's a good reason
解释你怎么没在上第二节课
you're not in second period right now.
他是费城人
So, he's from Philadelphia.
西费城  没错
West Philly, yeah.
但是他妈妈因为
But his mom is really freaked out
篮球场上发生的事吓坏了
about what happened on the basketball court,
所以她收拾好他的东西
so she packed up his stuff
让他搬到了洛杉矶
and -- and moved him to Los Angeles,
后来他就一直住在那里
and he's been living there ever since.
不好意思  篮球场上发生的那件事
I'm sorry, but was the thing on the basketball court
真的那么严重吗
really that big a deal?
竟然永远把自己的孩子送走
I mean, to send your kid away forever?
好像牵涉到黑帮
I think it involved gangs.
-他其实不是什么皇室  -当然了
- And he's not actually royalty. - No.
"清新王子"是他的街头诨名
"Fresh Prince" refers to his street cred.
日本的电视节目都很奇怪
TV in Japan is weird.
有那种游戏节目
There's all these, like, um, game shows
会让人做很疯狂的事
where they make you do insane things
比如  比如打扮成巨大的香蕉
like, um -- like dress up like a giant banana,
然后他们把你丢进动物园
and then they drop you into a zoo
跟一群一个星期没吃东西的黑猩猩关在一起
with a bunch of chimps that haven't eaten in a week.
然后你就吓坏了  尖叫着到处跑
And you're terrified, screaming, running around,
而演播室里有一群观众
but then there is this studio audience there
在看着你  嘲笑你
who's watching and laughing at you.
太可怕了
That sounds horrible.
我曾经上过电视
You know, I was on TV once.
代表IBM吗
For IBM?
不  我当时11岁  是感恩节游行
No. I was 11 -- uh, Thanksgiving Day parade.
我扮成朝圣者  另一个孩子穿着
I was a pilgrim, this other kid was wearing
他妈妈的棕色紧身衣和纸质羽毛
his mom's brown tights and construction-paper feathers,
我们在彩车上相互追赶  差点摔下去
and we chased each other around a float and almost fell off.
你能...稍等  稍等
Hey, can you just -- Like, one second, one second.
喂
Hello?
我小时候也上过电视
I was on TV when I was a kid.
《早安达拉斯》
"Good Morning Dallas."
揭露问题少年的节目吗
Troubled-youth exposé?
不是
No.
我赢了一场选美
I won a beauty contest.
你...
You...
什么
You what?
没错
Yeah.
无暇小姐  1970年
Little Miss Flawless, 1970.
我爸爸死后  我妈妈给我报名参加了选美比赛
My mom, um, signed me up for a pageant after my dad died.
她大概认为这样能分散我的注意力
I think she thought it would distract me
或是增进我们之间的关系之类的
or, uh, we'd bond or something.
然后你赢了
And you won.
那一次吗  没有  我输了
That time? No. No, I lost.
但她不停地给我报名
But she kept signing me up.
我和她说我不喜欢  但是她不听
I told her I hated it, but she...didn't listen.
有那么糟糕吗
That bad, huh?
一群八岁的小孩漂白牙齿
What, a bunch of 8-year-olds whitening their teeth
然后相互攀比长相吗
and getting ranked on their looks?
没错  就是那么糟糕
Yeah, it was that bad.
这么说你漂白过你的牙齿
So, you whitened your teeth.
天啊
Oh, my God.
她还有各种花样
She had a whole box of tricks.
用喷胶  给你的泳衣定型
Spray adhesive to -- to keep your bathing suit in place,
痔疮膏
Hemorrhoid cream.
-痔疮膏  -没错
- Hemorrhoid cream? - Yeah.
因为比赛前  我经常会哭
Yeah, 'cause I'd, um, cry a lot? Before the competitions?
我根本不想去
I didn't want to be there.
我想回家  所以我就哭啊哭啊
I just wanted to go home, and so I'd cry and cry.
这样整个人看上去就很浮肿
And that puffs you up pretty bad.
然后我妈妈发现
So my mom found out that
如果在眼睛周围涂上痔疮膏
if you put hemorrhoid cream all around my eyes,
就能消肿
it took the puffiness away.
这样我就能恢复正常  走上台
So I could be normal again and march out onstage
摆出漂亮造型
and do the Pretty Feet Pose.
一脚在前  一脚在后
One foot forward, one foot back,
手放在肋骨下方
hand underneath the rib cage,
脸上扯出愚蠢的笑容
big, stupid smile on my face.
然后...我就输了
And...I'd lose.
直到最后你赢了
Until you won.
是的
Yeah.
无暇小姐  1970年
Little Miss Flawless, 1970.
所有瑕疵都被遮住了
Got all those flaws taken care of.
等一下
One sec.
豪伊女士
Ms. Howe?
雅达利的加文·格林在找你
A Gavin Greene from Atari is trying to reach you.
谢谢
Thank you.
那么
So,
贝艾尔有没有什么清新王子
is there, like, a Fresh Princess of Bel Air?
逃课被停学是不是很蠢
Is it dumb to get suspended for skipping school?
是的
It is, okay?
但是我们并不是要讨论这个
But we're not here to debate that.
听着  我知道有一个
Okay? Look, I know what it's like
需要关注的哥哥或姐姐的滋味
to have an older sibling who requires a lot of attention.
你伯伯亨利就是个笨蛋
Okay, your Uncle Henry? Total bonehead.
总是会惹上大麻烦
Always getting into major trouble.
所以  家里人就不怎么关心我
And -- and so, I kind of flew under the radar.
海莉
Look, Haley...
如果你想撒撒气  没问题
...if you want to blow off some steam, fine,
但是不要做蠢事
just don't be dumb about it.
这不是你
You know, this isn't you.
你...很聪明
You're -- You're -- You're -- You're smart, you know?
你...是我们的基石  你...
You're -- you're our rock, you know --
亲爱的
Honey, Bug?
不  对不起
No. I'm sorry.
听着  不  我对不起
Look -- I don't... No, I'm sorry. Look, it --
听着...这不是什么大不了的事
Look, it's -- it's not even that big of a deal.
我...都没生气
I'm -- I'm -- I'm -- I'm not even mad.
这...
It's --
亲爱的  你...
Oh, sweetie, did --
谢普  我现在有点忙
Shep, I'm -- I'm kind of busy here.
你好  孩子
Ah, hey there, kiddo!
我让你难过了吗
Okay, look, did I upset you?
我说了什么或者...
Is it something that I said or...
不  我...
No, I'm...
-亲爱的...  -里面需要你  戈登
- Oh, honey -- - Kind of need you inside, Gordon.
-谢普  你要干什么  -里面需要你
- Shep, what do you need? - Kinda need you inside.
我过几分钟就来  好吗
Okay, well, I'll be there in a few minutes, all right?
好吧
Okay, sure.
-亲爱的  -我们在处理了
- Bug. - And we're on it.
-不  -可能不会有事的
- No. - Probably going to be fine.
想登录的用户显示信号忙
Busy signals for users trying to log on,
用户服务来电被打爆
the customer-service calls spiking.
流量缓慢
Uh, throughput's at a crawl.
虽然不是切尔诺贝利规模的灾难
We're not talking Chernobyl-style meltdown yet,
但得有三里岛
but we're in Three Mile Island
-那个规模  -等等  等等
- territory for suresies. - Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
都是因为固定费率模式吗
All because of the flat-fee model?
人们真的会在网上
I mean, are people really spending
多泡那么久吗
that much more time online?
许多人现在就开着电脑挂机一整天
A lot of people just leave their computers logged on all day now.
亲爱的  你能去办公室等我吗
Hey, Bug, do you mind waiting in my office for me?
有好几十个用户
We got three dozen users
已在网上挂了超过一天
who've been on for more than twenty-four hours.
那就强迫他们下线
So kick 'em off.
那我们得写新代码来实现
We'd have to write new code to do that
而且还得让所有人下载软件补丁
and then get everyone to download a software patch.
那我们需要世通提供更大带宽
Yeah. We need more capacity from MCI.
给我联系...乔恩·沃尔比
Get me, uh... Get me Jon Volpi on the phone.
打过了  联系不上
Uh, tried. Can't reach him.
那就打给艾伦  或者戴夫
All right, well, get me Alan or Dave
或者那个博比·苏巴洛
or that Bobby Sobrato guy.
他们也都打过了
Uh, we tried them, too.
世通那边一个人都联系不上
We can't get ahold of anybody at MCI.
乔在哪
Where's Joe?
他没来上班  我们也联系过他
Uh, he never came in. We tried him, too.
一直转语音留言
It just keeps going to voicemail.
那就
Look, just...
谢普  尽快想办法解决吧
Shep, we need to fix it fast, okay?
美国在线追杀得正紧呢
AOL is breathing down our butts, you know.
如果我们不能满足用户的需要
And if we don't give our customers what they need,
他们就会改去别家
they're gonna go somewhere else.
你知道怎么用Excel吗
Do you know how to work Excel?
知道
Yeah.
你能帮我把这些做成表格吗
Can you put these in a spreadsheet for me?
真的很重要
It's really important.
好吧
Okay.
最上面的抽屉有硬币
There's some quarters in the top drawer
需要什么的话就去售货机买
if you need anything from the vending machine.
好吗  我去去就回
Okay? I'll be right back.
这不像是海莉会做的事
It just doesn't sound like Haley.
是学校把她和琼妮弄混了吧
I was sure the school got her mixed up with Joanie.
并不是  我知道
Yeah, no, I know.
我跟你说  唐娜  我也不知道怎么回事
I'm telling you, Donna, I don't know what's going on.
她从来不是爱哭的孩子啊
She's never been the crying type.
是啊  就是...
Yeah, I mean, it was that...
那种哭得很厉害的状态
that... that really intense crying.
你越是想憋住  就越憋不住
Where you try and hold it in, but you can't,
到最后就哭得气都喘不过来
and, you know, then you just start going into convulsions.
没准她来月经了
Ah, maybe she's just on her period.
不是  唐娜  月经哭可不是这样的
No, Donna, this isn't menstrual crying.
相信我  我知道月经是怎么哭
Trust me. I know menstrual crying.
你还知道月经是怎么哭
Yeah. You know menstrual crying.
要不要我和她谈谈
Look, do you want me to talk to her?
不
No.
算了  我来处理吧
No, I'll... I'll handle it.
那好  祝你好运了
Okay, well, good luck.
周六下午  一望无际的大海
Saturday afternoon, nothing but ocean.
唐娜我跟你说  真是太美了
Oh, Donna, it was Goddamn beautiful.
所以我听着小曲睡着了
So, I took my little disco nap
然后我做了个梦
and I had a dream...
我变成了一个  又大又胖的
That I was this... I was this big, fat...
没毛娃娃在海牛肚子上晃啊晃
...bald baby just sloshin' around a manatee's tummy,
就这么摇过来  晃过去
just, "Whoosh, fworsh."
但是我一睁眼
But when I come to...
老天啊  我那船摇晃得天旋地转
...by God, the boat is pitchin' and it's yawin'
就跟头醉驴似的四处乱漂
and it's rollin' like a drunk donkey.
好大一场风暴突然就起来了
Just a freak storm out of nowhere,
那黑云就像堵墙挡着我没法靠岸
just a wall of black blocking my path back to the coast.
我算没辙了
I'm lost.
我就想  "关灯散伙吧  派对结束了"
And I'm thinking, "Turn out the lights. The party's over."
然后我就慌了
Then I started to panic.
然后我发疯似地发求救信号
Then I started to S.O.S. like an S.O.B.,
然后这两个书呆子开着船就过来了
and that's when these two eggheads just come cruising up.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
原来他俩的船上装了定制的GPS接收器
See, these two have a custom GPS receiver on their boat.
那是全球定位系统
That's the Global Positioning System.
没错  唐娜  就是那个
That is right, Donna, yeah.
原来弗雷德和比尔是工程师
Turns out Fred and Bill are engineers.
他们给AMD挣了好多钱
They made AMD a lot of money
把死贵的东西弄得超便宜
by making real expensive stuff real cheap.
-这技能很有用  -就是
- Not a bad skill set. - Right.
所以我们喝了几杯  就开始聊
So we had a few beers, and we get to talking.
我们就想着  干嘛不把他们的点子
And what we thought was, why not take their idea
推广做大呢
and scale it up?
做成像我这种人随处可以买到的东西
Make something a guy like me can buy off the rack?
佳明不是已经做出来了吗
Uh, doesn't Garmin already do that?
是  但是他们和麦哲伦
Mm, yeah, but them and Magellan
垄断了市场
got a stranglehold on the market,
而且  唐娜  他们定价贵得要死
and, Donna, they charge up the wazoo.
我们想把价格点拉下来
We're talking about disrupting the price point,
大幅度降低成本
bringing the costs way down.
有趣
It's interesting.
而且  这个技术真厉害
And, hey, I... what a fascinating technology.
是啊
It is, yeah.
我会研究一下的
I'll look into it.
-弗雷德  -是
- Fred... - Yes.
比尔
Bill...
幸会
Nice meeting you.
-认识您也很荣幸  -很荣幸
- Nice meeting you. - Pleasure.
-是啊  -谢谢
- Yeah. - Thank you.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
谢了  两位  大厅跟你们碰头
Thanks, guys. Great. I'll see you in the lobby.
-好  -很好
- Okay. - Beautiful. Okay.
待会儿见
All right.
待会儿去找你们
Yeah, we'll see you back there.
-好  -好的
- Yeah. - All right.
好吧
All right.
你就直说吧
Well, give it to me straight.
我得看看我可以期待什么
I got to manage my expectations here.
这个  很有趣
Well, um, it's intriguing.
你想在其中得到什么好处  博斯
What are you looking for out of this, Bos?
你真的想给创业公司当高管吗
I mean, do you really want to be the exec at a startup?
我只是想拿些中介费
I- I'm just looking for a finder's fee, you know?
我喜欢给人牵线搭桥  而且我喜欢这俩人
I like connecting people. And I like these guys.
而且  我就是这东西的目标群体啊
And just... I'm the market for this kind of thing.
知道吗
You know?
我这样的老水手还有不少呢
There's a lot of other salty sailors out there just like me.
那好吧  那我研究一下
Okay. Well, you know, I'll look into it.
真的  这技术很棒
Again, uh, what a technology.
那多谢你见我们
Well, thanks for having us in.
那多谢了
Thanks. Nice.
你  我和黛安早该一起吃顿饭了
Hey, you, me, and Diane are overdue for a dinner.
最近找时间聚一聚吧
We should do that soon.
好啊  聚吧
We should. Let's do.
聚吧
Let's do.
好吧
Okay.
好  我找到了
Okay, I found it.
死的明确形象毫无征兆地突然展现在大卫眼前
David was visited by an exact vision of death:
出自《鸽羽》  约翰·厄普代克著  杨向荣译
地上一个很深的洞  宽不过你的身体
a long hole in the ground, no wider than your body,
你被拽到洞里  而上面的白色面孔渐渐隐去
down which you are drawn while the white faces above recede.
你竭尽全力要够到他们
You try to reach for them,
可你的两条胳膊却像被钉住了一样动弹不得
but your arms are pinned.
一铲铲的土撒到你脸上
Shovels pour dirt into your face.
就这样  你将永远竖直地待在那里
There you will be forever, in an upright position,
眼不能见  耳不能闻
blind and silent,
谁都不会记得你
and in time no one will remember you,
谁也不会来看你
and you will never be called.
随着岩层的移位  你的手指会拉长
As strata of rock shift, your fingers elongate,
你的牙齿会斜刺里爆出
your teeth are distended sideways
把你的脸在地下扭成个大鬼脸
in a great underground grimace
跟一截粉笔没什么区别
indistinguishable from a strip of chalk.
大地继续翻滚  太阳慢慢断气
And the earth tumbles on, and the sun expires,
永远的黑暗将统治
and unaltering darkness reigns
曾是星斗满天的苍穹
where once there were stars.
我的天
Jesus...
但是这还不是故事的结局
But that's not the end of the story.
这个孩子的外婆让他
This kid... his grandmother tells him
去把谷仓里的鸽子都打死
to go shoot all the pigeons in the barn.
这让他开始思考死亡
And it makes him think about death,
而他的信仰也出现了危机
and he has this crisis of faith.
没人能让他安心
And nobody reassures him.
他被这种不可信感包围了
He is...surrounded by this non-belief.
就好像是一个阴谋  刚刚被他识破了
It's like a conspiracy, and he's just wising up to it.
但他还是把鸽子都打死了
But he still has to shoot all these pigeons.
一只不剩地全都消灭干净了
And he does, he just shoots the hell out of them.
然后他捡起一只死鸽子  开始端详它
And he picks up a dead pigeon, and he stares at it.
真的是太美了
And it's actually gorgeous.
就在这一刻  他想明白了
And he decides right then and there
一个把这么多的美丽倾注在一个
that no God who would give so much beauty
如此无用的生物身上的上帝
to such a worthless creature
是不会不让他获得永生的
would fail to let him live forever.
仿佛他的信仰恢复了
Like his faith is restored.
你也信这个吗
Is that what you believe?
我也  不知道
I just... I don't know.
我想我是...
I guess I...
我希望还有更多
I hope there's something more.
怎么了
"Huh" what?
只是觉得奇怪  从没想到你
Just weird. I never thought about you
会是那种需要"更多"的人
as the kind of guy who needed "more."
好吧
All right.
那你信仰什么
What do you believe?
这个嘛
Um, well...
我在日本见过这么一座庙
I saw this shrine in Japan.
当地人会把它拆毁
And, uh, the locals tear it down,
连地基都不剩  每20年一次
right to the foundation, every 20 years.
然后他们会重新盖一座
And then they build it right back up again,
盖得和原来一模一样
back to its original state.
他们已经这么做了1300年了
And they've been doing this for 1,300 years.
所有的部件都不是原先的
Nothing in it's original anymore,
但还是和当初第一天盖起来时完全一样
but it still looks identical to the day it went up.
听着真美
That's beautiful.
并不是
Well, no.
我倒不觉得这些人这么做
I mean, I don't think these people are doing it
是为了什么精神
for some spiritual reason.
我觉得他们这么做
I think they're doing it
只是因为他们放不下这个程序
because they're holding onto the process of it, you know?
这种做法本身就是其意义所在
The doing of it, that that's all that matters.
我是这么认为的
That's what I think.
我也不知道
I don't know.
我最近想从这里找到一些慰藉
I've been trying to find some solace in that lately.
结果怎么样
How's that working out for you?
不怎么样  乔
Not that great, Joe,
但是多谢关心
but thanks for asking.
我道歉
I'm sorry.
这样问  不太好
That was... That was unfair.
是啊  不太好
Yeah, it was.
我已经45岁了
Look, I'm forty-five.
没有成家  在地下室工作
I've got no family. I work in a basement.
一般没什么人找我寻求精神指导
People aren't exactly lining up for my spiritual guidance.
就是因为这个吗
Is that what this is about?
因为什么
What?
你说你还没成家
Well, you said you didn't have a family.
你并不想结婚的吧
You don't want one, do you?
我父亲去年春天去世了
My dad died last spring.
天啊  乔
Oh, God, Joe.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道这类事是什么样子  只不过
And you know what this is like, but...
你会开始思考一切
You just start to think about everything.
当我  15岁的时候
And when I was... when I was fifteen,
我发誓我绝对不要孩子
I made this vow that I would never have kids.
都是因为他
All because of him.
他是那么的  高大
He was just...huge
而且很  强势
and...imposing.
你知道你也高大强势吧
You know you're huge and imposing, right?
他让我觉得自己很渺小
He made me feel small.
就好像我
Like I was...
什么都不是
less than nothing.
而我绝对不想让我的孩子也有这种感受
And I never wanted to risk doing that to a child.
然后他死了
And then he died.
我  去了他的葬礼
And... And I'm, like, there at his funeral.
几乎没什么宾客去吊唁
And there's hardly anyone else there.
而突然间  他反而渺小了
And he felt like the small one all of a sudden.
因此你又想成家了
And that made you want to have a family?
这让我意识到我们不是一类人
It made me realize that we are different people...
而且
and, um...
也许我本来能做得更好
maybe I would have been better.
你想过要孩子吗
You ever think about kids?
想过
Yeah.
有一天  我突然对汤姆提起来了
I just, um, sprung it on Tom one day.
甚至都没怎么多想
Didn't even really think about it.
就一句"我们要孩子吧"
Just "Let's start a family."
这句话真是太蠢了
Such a stupid thing to say to someone
尤其如果你没打算让对方当真
if you're not ready for them to take it seriously.
他却当真了
And he did.
他简直乐死了
Oh, I mean, he lit up.
我从没见过人能开心成那样
I've never seen someone so happy.
于是我们就开始尝试
And so we, uh, started trying.
结果没成功
And it didn't work.
我则觉得松了口气
And I was relieved.
我松了口气是因为大自然替我做了
I was relieved that Mother Nature made a decision for me
我自己没胆量去做的选择
that I was too spineless to make for myself.
我意识到我只是想尽快完事
And I realized I was just going through with it
因为我不想再让他失望了
because I didn't want to disappoint him again.
抱歉  我不该这么说
Sorry. I shouldn't...have said that.
知道吗
You know,
能跟你认真聊聊太好了
it is so good to actually talk to you.
是啊
Yeah.
我也这么想
You too.
看来我得花些时间
I think it's gonna take a while
才能适应了
for me to get used to that.
拜托  "阿盖克"是什么鬼
I mean, come on. "Aggek"? What is that?
听起来像打嗝打疼了
It sounds like a painful hiccup.
让我联想起那种绿藻
It does kind of remind me of pond scum.
天啊  崔普简直要把我气死了
Oh, God, Trip makes my blood boil,
他那名字听着就气人
even just his name.
"崔普·基斯克"
"Trip Kisker."
伊莱亚斯倒是挺喜欢他的
Elias does like him, though.
他是个明星
He's a star.
如果我们想让你
Look, if we're gonna position you
接过我退休后留下的位置
to take over the mantle once I'm gone,
和明日之星搞好关系是没坏处的
a little diplomacy with the new star pupil won't hurt.
所以怎么样
So, how was it?
说实话
Be honest.
这个领域挺有潜力
It's a promising arena.
但我觉得他们有点晚了
But I think they're too late.
定位系统市场里已经有不少巨头了
There's a lot of muscle in GPS already,
零售环节又很难处理
and retail is tricky.
但我可以再深入研究下
But I can do some more digging,
或许组织人做个分析
maybe order up an analysis.
不
No.
我觉得约翰根本不在乎定位系统
I think John could care less about GPS.
他只是不愿闲着  想找点事做
He's just restless and looking for something to do.
"阿-盖-克"
"Aggek."
踩到小蜥蜴时它尖叫的声音
It's the cry you hear when you step on a tiny lizard.
我们还是可以在崔普背后
Hey, we can still talk trash about Trip
讲他坏话吧
behind his back, right?
-还是之后再回到这个话题上来吧  -是吗
- Let's circle back on that later. - Oh, really?
我觉得现在是深入考量的好机会
I think now's the perfect time to drill down on it.
我一向喜欢绕回来后
I always prefer to drill down
再深入考量
after I'm circling back.
柯蒂斯
Curtis.
我把软件的人都调去接服务电话
Yeah, well, I'm pulling software guys to handle support calls.
已经有用户取消了
And we've already had some cancellations.
那等你确定了再给我回电
Well, call me back when you do have an answer.
好吧  拜托告诉我
Okay, please tell me
你跟世通的人联系上了
you've talked to somebody from MCI.
联系了  我刚联系过
Yeah, we did. I just did.
巴里·施诺姆  施诺-汉姆
Uh, Barry Schnellham? Schnell-ham.
好吧  施诺姆是谁
Okay. Well, who the hell is Barry Shhhnellham?
巴里·施诺姆是...
Barry Schnellham is...
企业解决方案服务的临时经理
Interim manager of enterprise solution outreach.
他们要等到最后一刻
They're gonna wait out the clock
逼我们为更大带宽
and then squeeze us until we cave
大幅调高费率
on a huge rate hike for more pipe!
怎么...
What...?
看来客户服务部又倒霉了
Oh, it looks like customer service just face-planted again.
巴里·施诺曼
Barry Shhhnellham?
巴里·施诺姆  听着  谢普
Barry Schnellham? Listen to me, Shep.
你现在就给我打电话
You get on the phone right now
告诉巴里·施诺姆
and you tell Barry Schnellham
如果五分钟后乔恩·沃尔比
if I don't have Jon Volpi on the line
还不打过来
in the next five minutes,
我就亲自开车去一趟世通
I'm personally gonna drive down to MCI
拿我的脸打穿他的拳头
and put my Goddamn face through his Goddamn fist!
他怎么样
How is he?
很好  卡奈特很成功
He's great. CalNect is really successful.
-网络服务提供商部疯长  -不不不
- The ISP sector is growing like crazy. - No, no, no, no, no.
他到底怎么样
How is he?
应该还好
I think he's fine.
他不怎么说这些
He doesn't talk about it much.
肯定很可怕
It must be so scary.
他  真的真的很开心
I mean, h-he's, uh -- he's really, really happy.
至少之前很开心
Or at least he was.
直到我告诉他我的新点子
Until I told him about my new web idea.
是什么
Which is?
想象一下
So, imagine,
网页的网页
like, um, a website of websites,
组织性的索引  能帮你快速链接别的网页
uh, a curated index that takes you wherever you want to go.
就像黄页吗
Like the yellow pages?
不是  比那更好
No, it's -- it's so much more than that.
就像  像传送门...
It's like a -- It's a portal...
等等  稍等下
Wait. Wait. One second, one second.
我的想法是...好
...is what I'm thinking about -- Okay.
卡梅伦
Cameron.
你电话一天都打不通
Uh, your phone's been tied up all day.
是啊  抱歉
Yeah, sorry.
有时间吗
Um, you have a sec?
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
雅达利没人愿意推进
Nobody at Atari wants to push forward
一个没有调试好的产品
on a product that isn't perfectly calibrated.
所以我们决定先放一放
So we've decided to push back for a time.
放多久
How much time?
不确定
Indefinitely.
还有  我们需要你的声明
Also, we're gonna, uh, need a quote...
今晚之前
tonight.
好  我...
Yeah, uh, I'll, uh...
卡梅伦
Hey, Cameron.
他们...
They're, uh...
要延迟推出我的游戏
They're gonna delay my game.
而且...
Like, um...
不确定多久
indefinitely.
他们需要我的声明  用于新闻发布
They need some press-release quote from me,
所以  我得挂了
so I -- I should probably go.
我来写吧
I can write it.
让我帮你吧
Let me help you.
我们可以继续谈
Yeah, well, we can to talk about it more.
-然后茱蒂·巴尔盖斯进来了  -嗯
- So then Judy barges in room, right? - Yeah, yeah.
就像这样
Like that.
一点没错  就像这样
Exactly -- exactly like that.
好了  该谈谈
Okay, time to address
这屋里的高学历大人物了
the over-educated elephant in the room.
正式欢迎我们的新普通合伙人
A formal welcome to our new general partner --
克尔顿·马歇尔·基斯克尔三世
Colton Marshall Kisker III.
我们十分有幸
We were certainly lucky
能在去年把你从红杉抢来
to nab you from Sequoia last year.
欢乐行的首次公开募股  22X
And the JoyRide IPO -- 22X.
-干杯  -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
干杯
Cheers.
我有许多话想说
I've got a lot to say,
但我不想喋喋不休
but I don't want to ruin good champagne
而毁了好香槟  所以
with bad rambling, so...
很好
Great.
我很荣幸
I'm honored.
我很感激
I'm humbled.
我也准备好了
And I'm ready.
真的
I am.
我准备好深入考量我的投资组合
I'm ready to really drill down on monetizing my portfolio
同时培养有发展前景  收益颇丰的
while simultaneously cultivating new and promising ventures
新项目
that provide big exits,
让合伙人争着想签投资合同
with LP's clamoring to sign subscription docs.
非常感谢大家
So, thank you, one and all.
谢谢
Thank you.
好  欢乐时光到此为止  该干正事了
All right, fun's over. Back to business.
-好的  开始吧  -快坐
- Yeah. Let's do it. - Come on.
SparqPlug第二轮融资条款清单草案
SparqPlug's Series B term sheet draft
已经出来  可以先睹为快了
is available for the curious.
乔伊斯  你能分发PulseMD的目标吗
Joyce, can you send around the target for PulseMD?
好
Got it.
而千禧的帐面价值缩水了
And Millennium is a write-down.
我们先暂缓在网络上的投资吧
Let's take a knee on the web for now, yes?
其实不用
Actually, no.
流浪者正在改写他们的软件准备开展网络服务
Uh, Rover is repurposing their software for a web play.
他们正在孵化器里安顿下来
They're getting set up in the Incubator now.
你还在负责吧  唐娜
And you're still on point, Donna?
我提了谭雅·里斯做投资经理
I made Tanya Reese associate.
她会接手项目并在今天之内提交最新进展
She'll take lead and have an update by end of day.
我就提个建议
Just to throw out a quick suggestion --
流浪者有足够的空间重组他们的核心技术
Rover has enough runway to rework their core technology
并给整个网络做索引  供人搜索
and index the entire web, make it searchable.
这是低投入高回报的事
It's low-risk, high-reward.
抱歉  我只是在弄清一些细节
Uh, sorry, I'm -- I'm just getting caught up on the particulars,
但既然网络不太好做
but seeing as the web is rocky territory,
也许  回到浏览器上会
is -- is jumping back into browsers maybe something --
流浪者在开发的不是浏览器
Rover isn't developing a browser.
而是在制作全网络索引
It's indexing the web.
所有的
The whole thing.
我们可以先稍微回去一点
Uh, could -- could we circle back for a second
再深入考量一下领导问题吗
and drill down on leadership?
谭雅·里斯直到今天之前都是你的助理吗
So, Tanya Reese was an assistant of yours until today?
我们都知道这个  崔普
We're all aware of that fact, Trip.
没错
Absolutely.
我只是刚上轨道
I'm just -- just getting up on my skis here,
但她有网络相关背景
but, um, does she have a web background
或是与这个项目相关的管理经验吗
or any managerial experience specific to this play?
谭雅在我的桌上坐了两年
Tanya sat on my desk for two years.
她参与过许多交易
She's been involved in numerous deals
并在许多次成功中都扮演了重要角色
and consequential in the success of more than a few.
更不用说
Not to mention the fact
她从一堆申请中发掘了流浪者  所以
that she pulled Rover off the slush pile to begin with, so...
我只是在边想边说
Just, um, talking while I'm thinking,
但网络现在是个新鲜事物
but since the web is frontierland,
从外面引进一个顾问
would it be the worst idea
也不会很坏吧
to bring in an outside consultant?
我觉得谭雅完全可以
I think Tanya is perfectly capable
搞定这个挑战
of handling the challenge --
乔伊·温彻斯特肯定会乐意加入
I bet Joey Winchester'd be happy to come in.
你知道能来吗  迈克尔·霍滕多夫
You know who's available is Michael Hottendorf.
卡斯·莱因哈特三个月前刚从红杉公司离职
Cass Reinhardt just exited Sequoia three months ago
他绝对可以搞定这个
and he would hit this out of the park.
-卡斯  -我说
- Cass -- - You know what?
如果这是流浪者需要的
If that's what Rover needs,
我有个完美人选
I have the perfect person in mind.
等我去打个电话
Let me just, uh, make a phone call,
就回来汇报
and I'll report back.
好的  我们继续
Hmm, okay, moving on,
QwellX离目标差了一点
QwellX's missed its quarter by a bit.
利弗莫尔三能分担大约2%
Livermore Three can take about two percent of our load.
这就是杯水车薪
Oh, that's a drop in the bucket --
我们正焦头烂额呢
we're getting hit in the face with a fire hose.
这儿就像个灰狗长途汽车站  戈登
It's like a Greyhound bus station in here, Gordon.
博斯  你来做什么
Hey, Bos, what are you doing here?
我不知道  我就想顺道看看
I don't know. I just thought I'd stop by.
你生日那天我们没什么机会聊
We didn't get much of a chance to catch up on your birthday.
进我办公室吧
Hey, step into my office.
好
Okay.
看样子你需要趁机休息一下
Looks like you could use a break.
亲爱的  能出去一下吗
Hey, sweetie, can you give us a sec?
你好女士
Ma'am.
你有个年轻漂亮的秘书啊
Well, pretty, young secretary you got there.
我以为搞网络服务提供商是很轻松的
I thought the ISP business supposed to be easy-breezy.
外面的人都跟火烧屁股一般跑来跑去
People running around out there like their balls are on fire.
我们...
Well, you know, we're, um,
我们今天有点不太顺
we're going through a couple hiccups today.
我记得这样的日子
Yeah, I remember days like that --
一起扑火
the old bucket brigade routine.
但是  让你感觉好鲜活
By God, it makes you feel alive, though.
对吧  戈登
Doesn't it, Gordon?
不是吗
Doesn't it?
那些蓝人真有意思  是吧
Them blue -- Them blue men were something, huh?
-是的  -那鼓打的
- Yeah. - Their drummin'?
-他们都是蓝的吗  -听我说
- All their, uh -- their blue? - Hey, listen,
博斯  今天可能时机不好
Bos, m-maybe today's not a good time.
我们能过几天再出去喝一杯什么的吗
Can we grab a drink in a few days or something?
行啊  但是...
Yeah, yeah, but...
戈登
Gordon,
我得...找你借点钱
I need to, uh -- I need to borrow some money.
黛安和我之前想在
Diane and I were looking to invest
房地产上投点资
in this housing development.
她又不想做了  但我想
She lost interest. And I didn't.
所以我自己出了钱
Uh, so I put up my own money,
没有告诉她
without telling her.
然后我陷了进去
And then I went in whole hog.
所以我拆了东墙补西墙
So, you know, I-I put good money after bad
四处填坑  然后...
and bad money after worse, and before you --
现在我的钱都打了水漂
Well, now I'm in the drink.
第一笔银行账务还有一个星期就要到期了
First bank note's due in a week.
好吧  你怎么不找黛安帮忙呢
All right, well, I mean, why don't you ask Diane?
她毕竟是你妻子
I mean, she's your wife.
她还不是我妻子
W-Well, she's not my wife.
我不是吃软饭的人  我还得付赡养费
I'm not a kept man. I got alimony to pay.
还得给孩子们付大学贷款
I'm paying down college loans for the kids.
我...
I...
我把我的船卖了去还这笔钱
I sold my boat to pay this thing down.
你把你的船卖了吗  博斯
You sold your boat, Bos?
你欠了多少钱
Well, I mean, how short are you?
一万八
Eighteen thousand...
这只是第一笔款项
for the first payment.
博斯...
Bos...
你为什么来找我
Well, wh-why are you coming to me?
别担心  我还的起  还的起的
Well, now, don't worry, I'm -- I'm good for it. I'm good for it.
我现在手上有个定位仪的项目
No, I got this -- this GPS thing that I'm working on.
我还有...
And then I got, uh --
天呐  我还计划了好多项目
Oh, God, I got so much stuff in the hopper right now, really.
我只是资金周转不灵
I mean, I'm -- I'm just -- I'm just cash-shy,
只是有点周转不灵
just a little cash-shy.
所有我想你能...
So I figured you had a --
你觉得
You figured that...
我雇了群蓝人
since I hired the Blue Man Group
肯定兜里的钱多的放不下吗
that I must have cash just falling out of my pockets?
听着  博斯  我可以毫不犹豫地把钱给你
Look, Bos, look, I'd give you the money in a heartbeat.
但你在和黛安同居  她是我前妻的同事
But you live with Diane, who works with my ex-wife.
她的钱比我们所有人加起来的都多  好吗
And who has more money than all of us combined, all right?
我不能搅和进来
I can't get in the middle of that.
好吗  你得找她帮忙
Okay? You're gonna have to ask her.
我...
I...
那我们就完了
That'd be the end of us.
家里并不太平
Things are choppy at home.
但黛安就是我生命中的那个人
I mean, but Diane's it for me.
她一定是
She's got to be.
博斯  我得回去处理事情了
Look, Bos, I-I-I got to get back out there right now.
我不能...
I can't...
好吧
All right.
也不全都是钱的问题
It wasn't all about the money.
你不了解退休后的感觉
You don't know what it's like being retired.
你才刚刚四十岁
Hell, you just turned forty.
不管怎样  你还有很多事可做
You got a dozen more tricks up your sleeve no matter what.
我已经65岁了
I'm sixty-five.
我的人生不能就这样结束
This can't be my last thing.
你得去找她  博斯
You're gonna have to ask her, Bos.
海莉
Haley!
过来
Come here.
这是什么
Wh-What is this?
我刚休息了会儿  做了点别的
Oh, well, I just took a little break to make something.
我会继续查网站的  但是...
And I'll keep checking for broken sites, but --
不不不  没事
No, no, no. It's fine.
海莉  这幅画太赞了
Haley, th-that drawing is awesome.
因为是哈雷彗星
It's because it's Halley's Comet?
因为我叫海莉
Because I'm Haley?
很逊吗
Is that lame?
不  亲爱的  这一点也不逊
No, Bug, that's -- I-it's not lame at all.
你喜欢理查德·普赖尔吗
You -- You like Richard Pryor?
喜欢  他最棒了
Well, yeah, he's the best.
海莉  我不知道你能做这些
Haley, I had no idea that you could do all this.
标记语言挺简单的
Well, markup language is pretty easy.
又不像C++什么的
Not like it's C++ or anything.
那只小马穿的像个粉红色的小牛仔
That pony is dressed like a little pink cowboy.
其实是迷你马  这样更有型
It's actually a miniature horse. So it's way cooler.
这...
This is --
乔恩·沃尔比打来了
Jon Volpi. On the phone.
好的  谢普
All right, Shep.
太拉风了
Is rad.
-"拉风"吗  -拉风
- "Rad"? - Rad.
这很拉风  对
This is...rad, yes.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
准备好了  开始吧
Yes. Go ahead.
好
Okay, okay, okay.
"这么大规模的游戏不可操之过急
"A game of this scope can't be rushed.
雅达利团队和我建立了富有成效的工作关系
The Atari team and I have forged a fruitful working relationship
我们将继续给粉丝们带来
that will continue to deliver
他们所渴求且应得的
the engrossing gaming experience...
引人入胜的游戏体验
...our fans demand and deserve.
我很感激雅达利对这款游戏的支持
I am gratified by Atari's commitment to the title
也很期待我们日后的合作
and look forward to our ongoing collaboration.
另外  我坚决否认
In addition, I firmly deny
我有剥开加文·格林的头皮  挖走他的大脑
that I have an urgent desire to scalp Gavin Greene,
然后在空脑壳里拉屎的强烈愿望"
scoop out his brain, and shit in his empty skull."
棒
Yes!
我觉得可以这么发出去
I think we should send it.
当然很遗憾  得除去最后一部分
I mean, minus the, uh -- the last part, unfortunately.
我知道现在咽下这口气很困难
Listen, I know -- I know it's hard to swallow this right now,
但你很擅长你的工作
but you are so good at what you do.
乔
Joe --
我说真的
No, really.
别让那个混蛋夺走这一点
Don't let that asshole take that away from you.
他就是个寄生虫  你是个创造者
He's a parasite. You create.
你让事情从无到有
You make something out of nothing,
我一直很敬佩这一点
and I have always been in awe of that.
我不想破坏气氛
And not to ruin the moment,
但是我急着要去尿尿
but I really, really got to piss.
天呐  我也是  走吧
Oh, my God, me too. Okay.
乔恩  这个我们明白
Yes, Jon, we understand that part, okay,
但我们的干线完全被堵住了
but our trunk lines are totally clogged over here.
我们的合同上专门写明
Now, we had a contract that specifically --
我们会继续执行合同
And we'll uphold that contract...
但合同上没明确地
but that contract doesn't
定义扩张
explicitly codify expansion.
乔恩  我是运营部副总谢普·格拉玛蒂库斯
Uh, Jon, Shep Gramaticus, here, VP of Ops.
如果是费用问题  我们可以谈
Uh, if this is a rate issue, let's talk rates.
我们想谈
We want to engage.
资源太紧张了  谢普
It's crowded out there, Shep.
网络服务提供商市场上只有那么多带宽
Only so much bandwidth in the ISP market.
不是你想要就能有的
Can't really say there's pipe just laying around for you.
我们明白
Look, we get it.
我们可以多加钱
We'll break our rate lock.
乔恩  你就说实话吧
Look, Jon, just level with us, all right?
我们付多少钱才行
What do we got to pay?
几位  你们可能没听懂
Guys, I'm afraid you're not hearing what I'm saying.
不能再给你们带宽了  就是这样
There is no more pipe. For you. Period.
如果你们还有别的需求
And if you gentlemen need anything else,
可以找巴里·施诺姆
Barry Schnellham is your guy.
祝好
Take care, now.
我们成了没有主干网的网络服务提供商了吗
Are we an ISP with no backbone?
我们已经在大量损失用户了
We're already hemorrhaging customers.
来不及换供应商就已经完蛋了
Be dead before we switch providers.
他们怎么可以这样
Can they do this?
为什么要逼走我们
Why are they freezing us out?
他们自己要做网络服务提供商
They're starting their own ISP.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我们得请个外部法律顾问
We need to retain outside counsel.
他们不能这么做
They can't do this.
他们是公用事业公司
They're a public utility.
不能选边站
They cannot pick winners and losers.
这算一个人喝酒吗
Does this qualify as drinking alone?
算吧
It does.
你看见那个了吗
Oh, do you see that?
-什么  -月亮
- What? - The moon.
看窗外
Look out your window.
看不见
No.
可能是被山挡住了
I think the hill is blocking it.
真遗憾  这里看起来好美
That's too bad. It's so beautiful from here.
你错过了月亮
You missed the moon.
没办法
Oh, well.
今天是东南亚风味  菠萝柠檬草薄荷
Southeast Asian today -- pineapple, lemongrass, and mint.
谢谢
Thank you.
谭雅  等一下
Tanya, stay a sec.
我
I, uh...
发生了一点变动
There's been a slight change.
没骗你们
I kid you not.
我们从我刚说的那个小拖车那里穿过
We come up through that little trailer I was telling you about.
赤条条地穿过树林
We go through the woods, naked as a jaybird,
一边还弹着班卓琴
playing a banjo.
真没骗你们
I kid you not!
真的是这样  这该死的
It really happened, the son of a --
谭雅  你好啊
Hey there, Tanya. How are you?
我在和大家熟络一下呢
I'm just getting acquainted with these numbnuts here.
很高兴见到你  约翰
Good to see you, John.
我们开始吧
Should we get started?
好的
Sure.
这是一份短中期目标清单
Here's a list of short-to-mid-term goals,
-当然还有待商讨  -当然
- up for discussion, of course... - Of course.
主要针对接下来几周
...aiming at a product that we want to deliver
我们要开发出的产品
within the next couple of weeks.
你想好要什么了吗
So, do you know what you want?